export const QuizzData = [
    {
        "answers": ["Hogwarts", "Beauxbatons", "Koldovstoretz", "Uagadou"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What school does Harry Potter attend?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Tom Marvolo Riddle", "Albus Dumbledore", "Ronald Bilius", "Bellatrix Lestrange"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is the headmaster of the school Harry attends?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["William Weasley", "Lord Voldemort", "Leta Lestrange", "Harry Potter"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is Harry Potters greatest enemy?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Ron Weasley", "Dobby", "Hermione Granger", "Sorting Hat"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is Harry Potters closest friend (male)?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Ron Weasley", "Dobby", "Albus Dumbledore", "Hermione Granger"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is Harry Potters closest friend (female)?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Rugby", "Sepak takraw", "Quidditch", "Football"],
        "goodAnswer": 2,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What game, using flying broomsticks, is played by wizards?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Albus Dumbledore", "Severus Snape", "Quirinus Quirrell", "Gilderoy Lockhart"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What teacher, despised by many, teaches potions?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Owl", "Tortoise", "Pigeon", "Dog"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "And what type of animal is it?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Hagrid", "Bellatrix Lestrange", "Dobby", "Hermione Granger"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who tells Harry that he is, in fact, a wizard?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Albus Dumbledore", "J.K. Rowling", "J.R.R. Martin", "Joe"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who wrote the Harry Potter series?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Wakanda", "France", "Hogwarts", "United Kingdom"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "In what country are the books set?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["9 4/3", "7 3/4", "9 1/2", "9 3/4"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What platform does the train to the school depart from?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Dog", "Troll", "House elf", "Cat"],
        "goodAnswer": 2,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What type of creature is Dobby?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Ravenclaw", "Slytherin", "Gryffindor", "Hufflepuff"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What house is Draco Malfoy a part of?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Dursley's house", "Hogwarts", "Gringotts Wizarding Bank", "Azkaban"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What prison does Sirius Black escape from?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Lilly Potter", "Hogwarts", "Gringotts Wizarding Bank", "Azkaban"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What is Harry's mothers name?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Ravenclaw", "Slytherin", "Gryffindor", "Hufflepuff"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What house has the house colour of blue?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Candice", "Albus Dumbledore", "Dobby", "Fred"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is George Weasley's twin?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Hedwig", "Hermione Granger", "Dobby", "Lord Voldemort"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What is the name of Harry's pet?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Wand", "Horcruxes", "Mirror of Erised", "Owl"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What are Tom Riddle's diary and Rowena Ravenclaw's diadem?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Ron Weasley", "Dobby", "Gilderoy Lockhart", "Basilisk"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What creature, from the Chamber of Secrets, paralyzes and kills students in Harry's second year?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Cedric Diggory", "Albus Dumbledore", "Bellatrix Lestrange", "Dobby"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who dies during the Triwizard Tornament?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Hermione Granger", "Dementor", "Dursley's house", "Lord Voldemort"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What will \"suck all the happiness from you\"?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Bellatrix Lestrange", "Ron Weasley", "Moaning Myrtle", "Basilisk"],
        "goodAnswer": 2,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who haunts the girls bathroom?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Albus Dumbledore", "Luna Lovegood", "Madam Puddifoot", "Harry Potter"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who has radish earrings?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Locks", "Kills", "Heals", "Unlocks"],
        "goodAnswer": 3,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What does the spell \"Alohomora\" do"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Nagini", "Nigina", "Nagnai", "Ginina"],
        "goodAnswer": 0,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What is the name of Voldemorts snake?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington", "Hagrid", "Peeves", "Cedric Diggory"],
        "goodAnswer": 2,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "Who is the mischievous poltergeist that wreaks havoc throughout the school?"
    }, {
        "answers": ["Azkaban", "Yule Ball", "Hogwarts legacy", "Home coming"],
        "goodAnswer": 1,
        "category": "Basic Harry Potter Quiz",
        "question": "What ball does the school hold?"
    }
];